<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<items>
<item>
    <capt>Washington D.C. Release  – </capt>
    <desc>Today industry leader AMP unleashes the D.C. Release, packed with updates such as Optical Character Recognition (OCR), advanced Payment Processing and more – taking their Users to the next level. Thinking beyond what most think possible to create what inspires excellence, that’s the power of AMP.  
	</desc>
	<link>PR/Washington/index.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>AMP Technologies and Sysorex Announce Global Teaming Agreement – </capt>
    <desc>Companies to integrate technologies, deliver asset management and analytics for retail and commercial real estate property managers.
	</desc>
	<link>PR/Sysorex/</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>AMP Forges Powerful New Partnership with Loci Solutions – </capt>
    <desc>Silicon Valley, CA and Sydney, Australia – September 29th, 2015 – Loci Solutions, a leading property technology advisory team and AMP Technologies announced today a powerful partnership for the Commercial Real Estate Industry, bringing a new level of client experience to the marketplace.
	</desc>
	<link>PR/Loci/</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Miami Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies has combined the power of the revolutionary Asset Management Platform and the best leasing CRM app with the new Miami Release to create the most power asset management software for commercial real estate that is truly international
	</desc>
	<link>PR/Miami/</link>
  </item>

<item>
    <capt>SPARK – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies announced the latest mobile app SPARK. SPARK is the best new leasing CRM that enables Commercial Real Estate brokers to convert leads to revenue easily while staying connected to the office in real time, and it comes at no cost.
     </desc>
	<link>PR/SPARK/PipelineMobilePressRelease.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Manhattan Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies’ Manhattan Release is the most important upgrade in Asset Management software since AMP’s inception in 2010. By Placing an IRR and Valuation calculator directly on the home dashboard, AMP has taken the guesswork out of the value of properties and portfolios, and made making smart investments easier.
     </desc>
	<link>ManhattanRelease.html</link>
  </item>
	<item>
    <capt>Copenhagen Release – </capt>
    <desc>The Copenhagen Release is the latest technology in commercial real estate software and boasts a powerful new tool for managing single family assets. With the addition of a new single family segment, the only complete Asset Management Platform has now become an even more powerful tool than before.
      
   </desc>
	<link>CopenhagenRelease.html</link>
  </item>
	<item>
    <capt>Sydney  Release - </capt>
		<desc>Never before has there been a product for Commercial Real Estate that offers the level of innovation that AMP has brought with the Sydney Release. The Sydney Release, a shining achievement in a line of impressive product releases, combines AMPs traditional stacking plans with the ability to view multiple floorplans for multi-family assets along with enhanced security measures
         </desc>
	<link>SydneyRelease.html</link>
	</item>
	<item>
    <capt>MRI and AMP Technologies - </capt>
		<desc>MRI and AMP Technologies Forge a Powerful Global Partnership. Bringing a new level of innovation to the Commercial Real Estate marketplace with best of breed solutions from AMP Technologies and MRI. 
        </desc>
	<link>http://www.prweb.com/releases/2015/06/prweb12767468.htm</link>
	</item>
    <item>
    <capt>AMPPipeline Mobile App - </capt>
		<desc>The brand new AMPipeline Mobile App is the new frontier in real estate leasing. Now you can manage your entire pipeline anytime, anywhere, and from any device...
         </desc>
	<link>AmpPipelineMobileApp.html</link>
	</item>
	<item>
    <capt>Barcelona Release - </capt>
		<desc>With newly minted multi-family applications, the AMP Platform is even better than before.
        </desc>
	<link>BarcelonaRelease.html</link>
	</item>
	<item>
    <capt>Dubai Release - </capt>
		<desc>The booming metropolis in the dessert sets the scene for AMP's latest product update. With the tallest Commercial Real Estate tower, Dubai is the only place grand enough for AMP's big announcement
        </desc>
	<link>DubaiRelease.html</link>
	</item>
	<item>
    <capt>Centaurus Release - </capt>
		<desc>AMP looks to the skies for its newest product release. We have reinvented AMP's user interface to drive a more powerful performance
       </desc>
	<link>CentaurusRelease.html</link>
	</item>
    
   
   
	
	
    
</items>