<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<items>
<item>
    <capt>Washington D.C. Release  – </capt>
    <desc>Today industry leader AMP unleashes the D.C. Release, packed with updates such as Optical Character Recognition (OCR), advanced Payment Processing and more – taking their Users to the next level. Thinking beyond what most think possible to create what inspires excellence, that’s the power of AMP.  
	</desc>
	<link>PR/Washington/index.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Miami Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies has combined the power of the revolutionary Asset Management Platform and the best leasing CRM app with the new Miami Release to create the most power asset management software for commercial real estate that is truly international
	</desc>
	<link>Miami/</link>
  </item>

<item>
    <capt>SPARK – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies announced the latest mobile app SPARK. SPARK is the best new leasing CRM that enables Commercial Real Estate brokers to convert leads to revenue easily while staying connected to the office in real time, and it comes at no cost.
     </desc>
	<link>SPARK.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Manhattan Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies’ Manhattan Release is the most important upgrade in Asset Management software since AMP’s inception in 2010. By Placing an IRR and Valuation calculator directly on the home dashboard, AMP has taken the guesswork out of the value of properties and portfolios, and made making smart investments easier.
     </desc>
	<link>manhattan-release.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Copenhagen Release – </capt>
    <desc>The Copenhagen Release is the latest technology in commercial real estate software and boasts a powerful new tool for managing single family assets. With the addition of a new single family segment, the only complete Asset Management Platform has now become an even more powerful tool than before.
     </desc>
	<link>copenhagen-release.html</link>
  </item>
<item>
    <capt>Sydney Release – </capt>
    <desc>The Sydney Release builds on an already groundbreaking platform refining the experience and offering small changes in security that make a big difference. AMP’s Sydney Release takes asset management farther than it has ever been.
     
    </desc>
	<link>sydney-release.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Barcelona Release – </capt>
    <desc>Introducing the latest product release from AMP Technologies. Barcelona combines the overall power of the AMP Platform with a new customizable user interface and powerful occupancy forecasting technology to manage multi-family investments.
      </desc>
	<link>barcelona-release.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Dubai Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP's groundbreaking Dubai Release for commercial real estate creates a completely NEW way to quickly analyze and forecast revenue.
     </desc>
	<link>dubai-release.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Singapore Release – </capt>
    <desc>The Singapore Release focuses on AMP's mission of simplifying the User Experience. Now you can seamlessly share files on any mobile device across all Users and view your current and future revenue over your entire portfolio.
       </desc>
	<link>singapore-release.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Naples Release – </capt>
    <desc>Now available, the new Commercial Real Estate User Interface you can easily access on your phone and tablet. Users can easily view all their clients with one single log-in. Providing the ability to easily create and manage a pipeline in real-time across all devices.
       </desc>
	<link>NaplesRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Centaurus Release – </capt>
    <desc>Today AMP Technologies introduces their completely reinvented Centaurus User Interface. Users are able to seamlessly reduce operational risk, improve revenue health, and view key data insights all in real time.
       </desc>
	<link>CentaurusRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Boston Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP introduces their Boston Release, focused on driving performance with innovative advancements for the Commercial Real Estate Industry and connecting relative data to operational intelligence like never before.
     </desc>
	<link>BostonRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Santa Clara Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP today unveiled their Santa Clara Release, one of the most innovative releases in the industry. Providing users 50% faster speeds and advanced visual reports to manage and share key information in an amazing way.
       </desc>
	<link>SantaClaraRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Tokyo Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP announces its Tokyo Release that connects disparate data sources to drive relevant analysis to connect operational excellence, risk management and revenue growth. This June 17th – 20th AMP will introduce an innovative release and announce powerful partnerships at Realcomm.
       </desc>
	<link>TokyoRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Las Vegas Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Technologies has announced two exciting releases today at ICSC Las Vegas. The first release is the innovative offering of powerful Business Intelligence and Lease Analysis, and the second is the disruptive Las Vegas Release which includes key features which can enhance Real Estate business operations at a global scale.
       </desc>
	<link>LasVegasRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>New York Release – </capt>
    <desc>The release enables property managers and real estate investors to :
      Compare Rents and Improve Revenues
      Improve Planning with Lease Option Analysis
      Manage Pipeline Better, Visually
      Better Visibility into Leasing and Occupancy
      Better Strategic Management with Forecast of Building Occupancy.
    </desc>
	<link>NewyorkRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>San Francisco Release – </capt>
    <desc>AMP Announces Game Changing 'San Francisco' Release – Simple and Powerful Asset Management Experience, which You Have to See It to Believe It.AMP Technologies unveils its latest game changing release – San Francisco. In this release, real estate users will experience a cleaner UI with better typography, much tighter integration with Yahoo! and Google, and get access to data much faster.
      
   </desc>
	<link>SanfranciscoRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Hong Kong Release – </capt>
    <desc>Completely upgraded and redesigned AMP lease pipeline management with better collaboration with Property Managers and Leasing Brokers. It also features tighter control over access to data and ability to generate Summary and detailed reports with a click of a button.
      
    </desc>
	<link>HongkongRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Manhattan Release – </capt>
    <desc>Completely upgraded and redesigned lease abstracts with collaborative and cloud based tenant management.
      
   </desc>
	<link>ManhattanRelease.html</link>
  </item>
  <item>
    <capt>Monaco Release - </capt>
    <desc>Features you've requested. Brought to you in AMP's new release, Monaco. AMP's new release, codenamed Monaco, comes with features that you always needed, but never had, further enhancing the premier commercial real estate asset management product. From enterprise social extension to multi-building support, AMP's latest features will definitely excite you. Let's raise the curtains on them!
      
    </desc>
	<link>MonacoRelease.html</link>
  </item>
</items>
